[Generic]
[Generik]
Geyhatu for me ...
Geyhatu untukku ...
... what did you say Gündüz?
... apa yang kamu katakan Gündüz?
From the smell of Geyhatu ...
Dari aroma Geyhatu ...
Balgay didn't know what the language said.
Balgay tidak tahu apa kata bahasa itu.
Talk!
Berbicara!
Ah!
Ah!
Also from the laws ...
Juga dari hukum ...
... from your affairs ...
... dari urusanmu ...
... I did not know.
... saya tidak tahu.
That ...
Itu ...
... push ...
... mendorong ...
... until I bring me here and connect me.
... sampai saya membawa saya ke sini dan menghubungkan saya.
God!
Tuhan!
You will tell everything.
Anda akan menceritakan semuanya.
The meat ...
Daging ...
... until he could not keep his blood unofficial ...
... sampai dia tidak bisa menjaga darahnya tidak resmi ...
... I know you are full of holes.
... Aku tahu kamu penuh lubang.
Munchers are ready, Balgay.
Munchers sudah siap, Balgay.
Still no news from Tongar?
Masih belum ada kabar dari Tongar?
No, Balgay.
Tidak, Balgay.
His hand won't turn empty.
Tangannya tidak akan kosong.
Make this speak until I get back from Kocahisar.
Buat ini berbicara sampai saya kembali dari Kocahisar.
This is yours, Balgay.
Ini milikmu, Balgay.
Commander Laskaris ...
Komandan Laskaris ...
Don't return to the castle without finding Princess Sofia.
Jangan kembali ke kastil tanpa menemukan Putri Sofia.
Did you understand me?
Apakah kamu mengerti saya?
I swear on behalf of our Virgin Mary ...
Saya bersumpah atas nama Perawan Maria kami ...
... I will not return without finding the princess, sir.
... Saya tidak akan kembali tanpa menemukan sang putri, tuan.
Turks too ...
Turki juga ...
To the day when Mongolians came to our lands ...
Pada hari ketika orang Mongolia datang ke tanah kami ...
...damn it.
... sial.
Master Yannez, Osman Bey came.
Tuan Yannez, Osman Bey datang.
Bring it on.
Membawa pada.
Osman Osman!
Osman Osman!
Sofia.
Sofia.
Where is my daughter?
Dimana putriku?
When Selcan came from the mother oba ...
Ketika Selcan datang dari ibu oba ...
... to prove that you have it ...
... untuk membuktikan bahwa Anda memilikinya ...
... you showed me your dagger.
... Anda menunjukkan saya belati Anda.
I'll never forget Yannez.
Saya tidak akan pernah melupakan Yannez.
Sofia is in my hand.
Sofia ada di tanganku.
What did you do to him?
Apa yang kamu lakukan padanya?
Comfortable.
Nyaman
He sleeps like a lamb in his cage.
Dia tidur seperti domba di kandangnya.
He waits for his father to save him.
Dia menunggu ayahnya untuk menyelamatkannya.
If you do anything to my daughter ...
Jika kau melakukan sesuatu pada putriku ...
I came here to make a deal.
Saya datang ke sini untuk membuat kesepakatan.
If you leave me alive ...
Jika kau membiarkanku hidup-hidup ...
then Sofia survives.
lalu Sofia selamat.
What do you want from me, Osman?
Apa yang kamu inginkan dariku, Osman?
Balgay.
Balgay.
Leave!
Jatuhkan!
Late!
Terlambat!
You can't treat me like that, open my eyes.
Anda tidak bisa memperlakukan saya seperti itu, buka mataku.
Open my eyes!
Buka mataku!
Open!
Membukanya!
Bala Hatun.
Bala Hatun.
The circuit is back, Sofia.
Sirkuitnya kembali, Sofia.
Andre Salvador and Eleni ...
Andre Salvador dan Eleni ...
...where are they?
... di mana mereka?
There's no use in knowing them.
Tidak ada gunanya mengenal mereka.
I brought more important news.
Saya membawa berita yang lebih penting.
You like it very much.
Anda sangat menyukainya.
My father...
Ayah saya ...
... Sheikh Edebali ...
... Sheikh Edebali ...
... went to compile the valiant, ahis, who were thirsty for the gas.
... pergi untuk mengkompilasi yang gagah, ahis, yang haus akan gas.
Osman Bey has unimaginable accounts.
Osman Bey memiliki akun yang tak terbayangkan.
And the fire burning in front of your eyes ...
Dan api menyala di depan matamu ...
... you don't see armies carrying wood on that fire.
... Anda tidak melihat tentara membawa kayu di atas api itu.
Pity.
Kasihan.
This hyena wants a stronger bond.
Hyena ini menginginkan ikatan yang lebih kuat.
Let's cut the ropes, Zülfikar Derviş.
Mari kita memotong tali, Zülfikar Derviş.
Zülfikar Derviş.
Zülfikar Derviş.
Exit Press.
Keluar Press.
It won't be Bala.
Itu tidak akan Bala.
Whether I die or live, your end is certain.
Apakah saya mati atau hidup, tujuan Anda pasti.
You will disappear.
Anda akan menghilang.
Before I cut my judgment ..
Sebelum saya memotong penilaian saya ..
... measure your height, especially.
... mengukur tinggi badan Anda, terutama.
Take it ...
Ambillah ...
...little girl.
... gadis kecil.
You murdered Ahi Evran.
Anda membunuh Ahi Evran.
Sheikh Edebalı came.
Sheikh Edebali datang.
Fairly, Wrestler, Zulfikar ...
Cukup, Wrestler, Zulfikar ...
... Bud, dervishes ...
... Bud, darwis ...
Ahis came, Sofia.
Ahis datang, Sofia.
Had enough ...
sudah cukup ...
Osman Bey came.
Osman Bey datang.
Today ...
Hari ini ...
...Keep in mind.
... jangan lupa.
I don't forget. You forget.
Saya tidak lupa, Anda lupa.
Don't remember this state.
Jangan ingat keadaan ini.
Are you okay Bala Hatun?
Apakah Anda baik-baik saja Bala Hatun?
If I give Balgay to you ..
Jika saya memberikan Balgay kepada Anda ..
... Geyhatu washes the castle on our heads.
... Geyhatu mencuci kastil di kepala kita.
Sooner or later you know this will happen.
Cepat atau lambat Anda tahu ini akan terjadi.
I made an agreement with Balgay.
Saya membuat perjanjian dengan Balgay.
Why would I betray him?
Kenapa aku harus mengkhianatinya?
You both play games with each other.
Anda berdua bermain satu sama lain.
Who do you think will finally win?
Menurut Anda siapa yang akhirnya akan menang?
Are you...
Apakah kamu ...
... or Balgay?
... atau Balgay?
The two of you will crash into each other's throat at the first opportunity.
Kalian berdua akan menabrak tenggorokan satu sama lain pada kesempatan pertama.
You too...
Kamu juga ...
... I am the only one who can save my OB from Balgay.
... Saya satu-satunya yang bisa menyelamatkan OB saya dari Balgay.
And then?
Lalu apa?
The flood goes ...
Banjir berlanjut ...
stays on Yannez.
tetap di Yannez.
At that time...
Lalu ...
...also with you...
... denganmu ...
... with your daughter ...
... dengan putrimu ...
... we will also face the evil forces behind you.
... kami juga akan menghadapi kekuatan jahat di belakang Anda.
And you.
Bagaimana dengan kamu?
What about us?
Bagaimana dengan kita?
Tell, I'm listening to you.
Katakan padaku, aku mendengarkanmu.
Tomorrow...
Besok ...
... you will persuade Balgay to go to İnegöl tekfur.
... Anda akan membujuk Balgay untuk pergi ke İnegöl tekfur.
He will deliver his castle ...
Dia akan membebaskan istananya ...
... he will be convinced that he will receive gold and spoils with chests.
... dia akan diyakinkan bahwa dia akan menerima emas dan rampasan dengan peti.
After leaving Balgay's headquarters ...
Setelah meninggalkan markas Balgay ...
... I know which way to go with his soldiers.
... Aku tahu ke mana harus pergi dengan tentaranya.
Are you going to ambush him on İnegöl road?
Apakah Anda akan menyergapnya di jalan İnegöl?
We will both get rid of Balgay.
Kami berdua akan menyingkirkan Balgay.
With a handful of Alp ...
Dengan sedikit Alp ...
... do you think he can handle his soldiers?
... apakah kamu pikir dia bisa menangani tentaranya?
This is my matter.
Ini masalah saya.
Let's say you killed Balgay.
Katakanlah Anda membunuh Balgay.
When you're done ...
Setelah selesai ...
How do I know that you will give my daughter back to me?
Bagaimana saya tahu bahwa Anda akan memberikan anak saya kembali kepada saya?
You will rely on the words of Osman, son of Ertuğrul Gazi.
Anda akan mengandalkan kata-kata Osman, putra Ertuğrul Gazi.
Soldiers.
Tentara.
Hostility is another trust.
Permusuhan adalah kepercayaan lain.
I can trust you.
Aku bisa mempercayaimu
But...
Namun ...
... big cases ...
... kasus besar ...
... does not walk with confidence.
... tidak berjalan dengan percaya diri.
As the engagement sign between us ...
Sebagai tanda pertunangan di antara kami ...
I will give you the laws of Genghis Khan.
Aku akan memberimu hukum Jenghis Khan.
When the time comes, take her daughter and ...
Ketika saatnya tiba, bawa putrinya dan ...
..you will give the laws.
..you akan memberikan hukum.
What if you die?
Bagaimana jika kamu mati?
The laws of Genghis Khan ...
Hukum Jenghis Khan ...
... is more precious to us than Sofia.
... lebih berharga bagi kita daripada Sofia.
When the time comes ...
Ketika saatnya tiba ...
... you will get your daughter ...
... kamu akan mendapatkan putrimu ...
... you're going to give the laws. That's all.
... Anda akan memberikan hukum. Itu saja.
What about you ...
Bagaimana dengan kamu ...
... and take the laws and ...
... dan mengambil hukum dan ...
... if I sacrifice my daughter?
... jika aku mengorbankan putriku?
You will not give up on your dreams of making Sofia the queen of Constantine, Yannez.
Anda tidak akan menyerah pada impian Anda untuk menjadikan Sofia ratu Constantine, Yannez.
You are nothing without Sofia.
Anda bukan apa-apa tanpa Sofia.
What happens now, sir?
Apa yang terjadi sekarang, tuan?
Is there any destim, sir?
Apakah ada tujuan, tuan?
You're coming.
Anda datang.
Slowly, what is this state?
Perlahan, apa kondisi ini?
Time is not time to be slow, sir.
Waktu bukanlah waktu untuk lambat, tuan.
Gündüz has become the beginning of Gündüz.
Gündüz telah menjadi awal dari Gündüz.
Tell me.
Beritahu saya
Guys I ...
Guys Saya ...
... We found two Alps of Gündüz Bey.
... Kami menemukan dua Alps di Gündüz Bey.
There is no trace from Gündüz Bey.
Tidak ada jejak dari Gündüz Bey.
Who killed?
Siapa yang membunuh
We don't know, sir.
Kami tidak tahu, tuan.
Why did he come out of the day?
Kenapa dia keluar hari ini?
Where would he go?
Kemana dia akan pergi?
He found Osman and went to join Osman's cengine.
Dia menemukan Osman dan pergi untuk bergabung dengan cengine Osman.
Have you grown in cengi now?
Sudahkah Anda tumbuh di cengi sekarang?
His war is different ...
Perangnya berbeda ...
... is our cultivar separate?
... Apakah kultivar kita terpisah?
HE.
HE.
It's separate.
Itu terpisah.
When Kayı chose Mongolian, our ceremony was reserved.
Ketika Kayı memilih Mongolia, upacara kami dicadangkan.
Our unofficial person is also separate.
Orang tidak resmi kami juga terpisah.
Then when your head is stuck ...
Lalu ketika kepala Anda macet ...
... I burned Why do you run to my door because of Allah?
... Saya terbakar Mengapa Anda lari ke pintu saya karena Allah?
Why can't you ask Osman for help?
Mengapa Anda tidak bisa meminta bantuan Osman?
Osman is on the run.
Osman sedang dalam pelarian.
If you search, you won't find it.
Jika Anda mencari, Anda tidak akan menemukannya.
If you found ...
Jika Anda menemukan ...
... You can not keep.
... Anda tidak bisa terus.
Even when you're in trouble ...
Bahkan ketika Anda dalam kesulitan ...
... you don't pay allegiance ...
... kamu tidak membayar kesetiaan ...
... you take refuge in my principality.
... Anda berlindung di kerajaan saya.
At that time...
Lalu ...
... look at your state at a turn.
... lihat keadaanmu secara bergantian.
Those who follow Osman ...
Mereka yang mengikuti Osman ...
... where is the door he hopes for ...
... di mana pintu yang dia harapkan ...
... remember it well.
... ingat baik-baik.
Let the Alps be thoroughly surrounded.
Biarkan Alpen dikelilingi sepenuhnya.
What do you do, sir? Where will you go?
Apa yang Anda lakukan, Tuan? Kemana Anda akan pergi?
I must see Balgay.
Saya harus melihat Balgay.
Gündüz went after Osman. What should Balgay do?
Gündüz mengejar Osman, apa yang harus dilakukan Balgay?
Do you ever say you don't mix it up?
Apakah Anda pernah mengatakan Anda tidak mencampuradukkannya?
Mongolian is everywhere, chick.
Mongolia ada di mana-mana, cewek.
Maybe they have something they see and hear.
Mungkin mereka memiliki sesuatu yang mereka lihat dan dengar.
Let's go and learn. Batur ...
Ayo pergi dan belajar. Batur ...
... my son will come with me.
... anakku akan ikut aku.
With thick milk.
Dengan susu kental.
Mr. Osman.
Osman Bey.
Siblings.
Brothers.
I Usman.
Aku Usman.
What did you do, Osman?
Apa yang kamu lakukan, Osman?
Yannez accepted my offer.
Yannez menerima tawaran saya.
We will trap Balgay.
Kami akan menjebak Balgay.
In the end, it's time.
Pada akhirnya, saatnya.
What is your intention, Osman Bey, to take Balgay?
Apa niat Anda, Osman Bey, untuk mengambil Balgay?
No. Take your life.
Tidak. Ambil hidupmu.
Abad with persecution ...
Abad dengan penganiayaan ...
... we'll show him that he finally sucks.
... kami akan menunjukkan kepadanya bahwa dia akhirnya payah.
He will see Balgay and his stooges ...
Dia akan melihat Balgay dan antek-anteknya ...
... great plane trees ...
... pohon pesawat besar ...
... grows in stormy lands.
... Tumbuh di tanah badai.
Those who try to cut our branch ...
Mereka yang mencoba memotong cabang kami ...
... we will remove the root from the soil.
... kami akan menghapus root dari tanah.
Oh dear!
Oh sayang!
Allahu akbar!
Allahu akbar!
Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
Guys I ...
Guys Saya ...
... Mr. Gündüz ...
... Tn. Gündüz ...
What happened to my brother?
Apa yang terjadi pada saudaraku?
They missed Gündüz Bey, they seek him everywhere.
Mereka merindukan Gündüz Bey, mereka mencarinya di mana-mana.
What do you say, Erkut?
Bagaimana menurutmu, Erkut?
Balgay.
Balgay.
Balgay!
Balgay!
That's Balgay's job.
Itu pekerjaan Balgay.
He wants to know who sent the news to Geyhatu.
Dia ingin tahu siapa yang mengirim berita ke Geyhatu.
To see.
Untuk melihat.
Come on, valiant, come on!
Ayo, berani, ayo!
We go to Balgay's quarters.
Kami pergi ke tempat tinggal Balgay.
Guys I ...
Guys Saya ...
... wait for the night for the raid?
... tunggu malam untuk serangan itu?
Balgay pus now goes to the castle.
Balgay nanah sekarang pergi ke kastil.
He must be holding my brother at the headquarters.
Dia pasti menggendong adikku di markas.
It's time. Come on!
Sudah waktunya, ayo!
Thread ...
Thread ...
... you stay here.
... kamu tinggal di sini.
A little scratch, sir.
Sedikit goresan, tuan.
You can speak this jackal.
Anda dapat berbicara serigala ini.
This is the dog that killed Köni himself.
Ini adalah anjing yang membunuh Köni sendiri.
We need to learn Balgay's games.
Kita perlu belajar permainan Balgay.
The information we will take to Geyhatu will pull his rope.
Informasi yang akan kami bawa ke Geyhatu akan menarik talinya.
Let's.
Ayo.
He ...
Dia ...
... Topic ...
... Topik ...
... keep an eye on him.
... awasi dia.
Thank you sir.
Terima kasih tuan
What the hell do you do? Tell me.
Apa yang kamu lakukan? Katakan padaku.
What would you like, chick?
Apa yang kamu suka, cewek?
You said I'll send clothes to Batur.
Anda bilang saya akan mengirim pakaian ke Batur.
They ambushed Bala.
Mereka menyergap Bala.
Now Day ...
Sekarang hari ...
... was attacked for no reason.
... diserang tanpa alasan.
Well, why?
Nah, mengapa?
Who is under them?
Siapa yang ada di bawah mereka?
Enough.
Cukup.
That will not do.
Itu tidak akan melakukannya.
If you are involved in these,
Jika Anda terlibat dalam ini,
... I'll scrape those eyes, Zöhre.
... Aku akan mengorek mata itu, Zöhre.
What do you imply, chick?
Apa maksudmu, cewek?
What matters is not what I imply.
Yang penting bukan yang saya maksudkan.
The important thing is the anxiety you can't hide.
Yang penting adalah kecemasan yang tidak bisa Anda sembunyikan.
What have you done to Sofia?
Apa yang telah kamu lakukan pada Sofia?
It seemed out of war.
Tampaknya keluar dari perang.
He deserved.
Dia layak.
You all ...
Anda semua ...
... can you give it what you deserve, Bala?
... bisakah kamu memberikan apa yang pantas kamu dapatkan, Bala?
You should also give Osman Bey the right, Bala.
Anda juga harus memberi Osman Bey hak, Bala.
Your love is not the love that will lose.
Cintamu bukanlah cinta yang akan hilang.
I thought a lot, Gonca.
Saya banyak berpikir, Gonca.
If I was married to Osman when I was in this state ...
Jika saya menikah dengan Osman ketika saya berada di negara ini ...
... it would be unfair to him.
... itu tidak adil baginya.
No, Balaam.
Tidak, Bileam.
If you tell Osman Bey about the situation ...
Jika Anda memberi tahu Osman Bey tentang situasinya ...
... no injustice.
... tidak ada ketidakadilan.
Of course I won't marry Gonca.
Tentu saja aku tidak akan menikahi Gonca.
That's not the point.
Bukan itu intinya.
Even if I say, Osman does not give up.
Bahkan jika saya katakan, Osman tidak menyerah.
He does not leave his love.
Dia tidak meninggalkan cintanya.
Then...
Lalu ...
... wants time over time.
... ingin waktu ke waktu.
Whether it.
Apakah itu.
It is right.
Hal itu benar.
Then it takes either a chick.
Maka dibutuhkan salah satu cewek.
Either he agrees to life without children.
Entah dia setuju untuk hidup tanpa anak-anak.
Then what happens to us, Gonca?
Lalu apa yang terjadi pada kita, Gonca?
Talk Day!
Hari Bicara!
What did you tell Geyhatu Gündüz?
Apa yang kau katakan pada Geyhatu Gündüz?
Did you tell Geyhatu that the laws were in Balgay?
Apakah Anda memberi tahu Geyhatu bahwa hukum ada di Balgay?
Say...
Jadi ...
... Balgay ...
... Balgay ...
... Geyhatu the ...
... Geyhatu yang ...
... turns around after him.
... berbalik setelahnya.
If I were you, I would talk before Balgay came.
Jika aku jadi kamu, aku akan bicara sebelum Balgay datang.
Think about what he will do to you.
Pikirkan tentang apa yang akan dia lakukan pada Anda.
Think about it.
Pikirkan tentang itu.
Cerkutay ...
Cerkutay ...
... take my life.
... ambil hidupku.
Otherwise, you should know that I don't put this next to you.
Kalau tidak, Anda harus tahu bahwa saya tidak meletakkan ini di sebelah Anda.
You know.
Anda tahu.
Take my life.
Ambil hidupku.
Your death will not be easy Day.
Kematianmu tidak akan mudah.
But not my hand.
Tapi bukan tanganku.
From Balgay's hand.
Dari tangan Balgay.
Writhing.
Menggeliat.
Slowly.
Secara bertahap.
Mr. Gündüz ...
Tuan Gündüz ...
... God help you.
... Tuhan membantumu.
Beyim has tied Gündüz Bey in the square.
Beyim telah mengikat Gündüz Bey di alun-alun.
The Cerkutay dog ​​torments him at the beginning.
Anjing Cerkutay menyiksanya di awal.
That's what it means to hurt Bala.
Itulah artinya menyakiti Bala.
He thinks that it was my brother who brought news to Geyhatu.
Dia berpikir bahwa saudaraku yang membawa berita ke Geyhatu.
Gündüz Bey also does not speak to the Oba not to feel bad.
Gündüz Bey juga tidak berbicara dengan Oba untuk tidak merasa buruk.
You are watching the way.
Anda memperhatikan jalannya.
Thank you sir.
Terima kasih tuan
You should listen to me well.
Anda harus mendengarkan saya dengan baik.
There are sentry sentries posted around the headquarters.
Ada penjaga yang diposting di sekitar kantor pusat.
The troops of Balgay are also patrolling.
Pasukan Balgay juga berpatroli.
Eighty neutrals exist in Söğüt.
Delapan puluh netral ada di Söğüt.
So much went to the castle.
Begitu banyak yang pergi ke kastil.
There are also a large number of soldiers at the headquarters.
Ada juga sejumlah besar tentara di markas.
We will crash into the hills like lightning at once.
Kami akan menabrak bukit seperti kilat sekaligus.
Samsa Bey ...
Samsa Bey ...
It will come by the orient and garp of the Alps.
Itu akan datang dengan orientasi dan gawang Alpen.
Thank God for my Lord who does not blind my pus.
Terima kasih Tuhan untuk Tuhanku yang tidak membutakan nanahku.
Come on then valiant.
Ayo berani.
Let's.
Ayo.
I can't see the tekfur that will pay me allegiance.
Saya tidak bisa melihat tekfur yang akan memberi saya kesetiaan.
Where are they, Yannez?
Di mana mereka, Yannez?
They came.
Mereka datang.
They said they would pay you allegiance.
Mereka bilang mereka akan membayarmu.
They brought their gifts.
Mereka membawa hadiah mereka.
You...
Anda ...
I said where are they
Saya katakan di mana mereka
... Yannez.
... Yannez.
I sent them all back.
Saya mengirim mereka semua kembali.
Look at me, old man ...
Lihat aku, orang tua ...
Do you play Balgay?
Apakah Anda bermain Balgay?
Osman...
Osman ...
What happened to Osman?
Apa yang terjadi pada Osman?
my daughter caught Sofia.
putri saya menangkap Sofia.
Where is Osman?
Dimanakah Osman?
He was here a little while ago.
Dia ada di sini beberapa saat yang lalu.
Osman came to his feet.
Osman bangkit berdiri.
You left him too?
Anda meninggalkannya juga?
Don't forget, my daughter ...
Jangan lupa, putriku ...
... your queen is in your hand.
... ratu Anda ada di tangan Anda.
For Sofia ...
Untuk Sofia ...
What did he ask you for?
Apa yang dia minta darimu?
You.
Anda.
For my daughter's life ...
Untuk hidup putriku ...
... wanted your life.
... menginginkan hidupmu.
What did you say?
Apa yang kamu katakan
If I kill Balgay while he is a guest on the pen ...
Jika saya membunuh Balgay saat dia menjadi tamu di kandang ...
... that Geyhatu would destroy the castle.
... bahwa Geyhatu akan menghancurkan kastil.
You said it right.
Anda mengatakannya dengan benar.
O Osman ...
O Osman ...
...what did he say?
apa yang dia katakan?
I will do this work. You just bring it to me, take your daughter, he said.
Saya akan melakukan pekerjaan ini. Anda hanya membawanya kepada saya, ambil putri Anda, katanya.
Where to take it ...
Ke mana bawa ...
... you will throw me in the lap of Osman?
... Anda akan melemparkan saya di pangkuan Osman?
Tomorrow he will go to İnegöl tekfur ...
Besok dia akan pergi ke İnegöl tekfur ...
I said that the castle would collapse.
Saya mengatakan bahwa kastil akan runtuh.
He is in the gate on the way to the castle
Dia ada di gerbang menuju kastil ...
... he will trap you.
... dia akan menjebakmu.
You said good.
Kamu bilang bagus.
You will bring Osman back to me so I can take my daughter away from you, Balgay.
Kamu akan membawa Osman kembali kepadaku sehingga aku bisa mengambil putriku darimu, Balgay.
If my daughter dies ...
Jika putri saya meninggal ...
I'll bury Constantinepolis dreams.
Saya akan mengubur mimpi Konstantinepolis.
Know it.
Ketahuilah itu.
Osman.
Osman.
They're Balgay's prisoner!
Mereka adalah tahanan Balgay!
What did you do bro?
Apa yang kamu lakukan kawan?
You mind ...
Kamu keberatan ...
... did you add to dry bread, brother?
... apakah Anda menambahkan roti kering, saudara?
What are you doing here?
Apa yang kamu lakukan disini
Brother...
Saudaraku ...
...are you okay?
Apakah kamu baik-baik saja?
Are you okay, brother?
Apakah kamu baik-baik saja, saudara?
I had a hope until you came ...
Saya punya harapan sampai Anda datang ...
... no more.
... tidak lagi.
Samsa Sergeant.
Sersan Samsa.
The Bams.
The Bams.
Osman.
Osman.
I knew you would make a madness for your brother ...
Aku tahu kamu akan membuat kegilaan untuk saudaramu ...
I wouldn't expect that much.
Saya tidak akan berharap banyak.
Bravery doesn't even suit your mouth.
Keberanian bahkan tidak sesuai dengan mulutmu.
Your bravery for lonely girls ...
Keberanianmu untuk gadis-gadis yang kesepian ...
... take it off to tied hands.
... lepaskan ke tangan yang diikat.
I missed Bala Hatun.
Saya merindukan Bala Hatun.
But you will not be able to escape.
Tetapi Anda tidak akan bisa melarikan diri.
You will die with your brother.
Anda akan mati bersama saudaramu.
You came to Balgay's hell with your own foot.
Anda datang ke neraka Balgay dengan kaki Anda sendiri.
Hang them on the hooks.
Gantungkan pada kaitnya.
Let their meat be hung until it gets tasted.
Biarkan daging mereka digantung sampai dicicipi.
As for Balgay, we have a feast.
Adapun Balgay, kami memiliki pesta.
I will prepare you such a feast.
Saya akan mempersiapkan Anda pesta seperti itu.
You can't get enough of your own flesh.
Anda tidak bisa mendapatkan cukup daging Anda sendiri.
Instead of who ...
Alih-alih yang ...
I will drink your own blood.
Aku akan minum darahmu sendiri.
Hang Osman first.
Gantung Osman dulu.
Either freedom ...
Entah kebebasan ...
... martyrdom.
... mati syahid.
Mahallah like a fortress wall.
Mahallah seperti tembok benteng.
Fortunately, we took our precaution.
Untungnya, kami mengambil tindakan pencegahan kami.
Allahu akbar! Shoot the coach brave!
Allahu akbar! Tembak pelatih dengan berani!
Shoot the valiant!
Tembak yang gagah berani!
Osman...
Osman ...
Alişar Bey came out somewhat darker than I thought.
Alişar Bey keluar agak lebih gelap dari yang saya kira.
No one dared to press Balgay's headquarters to this day.
Tidak ada yang berani menekan markas Balgay hingga hari ini.
It is Melik.
Itu Melik.
He is so blind that he is too blind to see even the trouble coming to himself.
Dia begitu buta sehingga dia terlalu buta untuk melihat bahkan kesulitan datang pada dirinya sendiri.
When hearing what happened, Geyhatu will pull the rope of Balgay himself with his own hands.
Saat mendengar apa yang terjadi, Geyhatu akan menarik tali Balgay sendiri dengan tangannya sendiri.
Until that beautiful day ...
Sampai hari yang indah itu ...
... I will bury Osman and Dündar.
... Aku akan menguburkan Osman dan Durar.
We came here to carry soil to the grave of our enemies.
Kami datang ke sini untuk membawa tanah ke kuburan musuh kami.
Look at the wisdom of Allah that ...
Lihatlah kebijaksanaan Allah bahwa ...
... before us, our enemies buried each other.
... sebelum kita, musuh kita saling mengubur.
My brother.
Adikku.
Big brother, big brother.
Kakak laki-laki, kakak
Osman.
Osman.
Are you okay, brother?
Apakah kamu baik-baik saja, saudara?
I'm fine, brother, I'm fine.
Saya baik-baik saja, saudara, saya baik-baik saja.
Mr. Bamsı ...
Tuan Bamsi ...
... my brother is entrusted to you.
... saudaraku dipercayakan padamu.
Melik, take out the dishes from the majesty ...
Melik, ambil piring dari keagungan ...
... let's enjoy the view.
... mari kita nikmati pemandangannya.
Let's watch the roar.
Mari kita saksikan aumannya.
Bey.
Bey.
You call it valiant ...
Anda menyebutnya gagah ...
Cerkutay, whirling.
Cerkutay, berputar.
When you see it sooner ...
Ketika Anda melihatnya lebih cepat ...
... the crap flowed from his stance.
... omong kosong mengalir dari posisinya.
Come on, Turkish.
Ayo, Turki.
Take a taste of my pusat that has shed the blood of many beeches.
Rasakan cita rasa pusat saya yang telah menumpahkan banyak darah beech.
Come on. Come on blood shit.
Ayo, cepatlah.
Come on ...
Ayo ...
... the calculation of the blood of all the valiant ...
... perhitungan darah semua yang gagah berani ...
Give me ...
Berikan aku ...
This is for Bala.
Ini untuk Bala.
This is for my brother.
Ini untuk saudaraku.
This is for many brave people.
Ini untuk banyak orang pemberani.
Our account is not over with you Cerkutay.
Akun kami belum berakhir dengan Anda Cerkutay.
He's not finished.
Dia tidak selesai.
Shoot the valiant!
Tembak yang gagah berani!
We crossed the snowy mountains.
Kami melintasi pegunungan bersalju.
We were Boran and overflowed Bamsı Bey.
Kami adalah Boran dan meluap Bamsı Bey.
We hired the camps, Samsa Bey.
Kami menyewa kamp, ​​Samsa Bey.
Hey, thank you.
Hei, terima kasih.
Brother.
Adikku.
My Osman remained on carrion.
Osman saya tetap di bangkai.
Let's be thesis.
Mari menjadi tesis.
Let's go before Balgay iti come from the castle.
Ayo pergi sebelum Balgay iti datang dari kastil.
Erkut.
Erkut.
Guys I ...
Guys Saya ...
... Dundar Bey and Batur Bey come, and we have horses with him.
... Dundar Bey dan Batur Bey datang, dan kami membawa kuda.
Erkut ...
Erkut ...
... take Gündüz Bey.
... ambil Gündüz Bey.
Osman...
Osman ...
... let's not do this, brother.
... jangan lakukan ini, saudara.
You can leave before Balgay comes, brother.
Anda dapat pergi sebelum Balgay datang, saudara.
It's account time.
Saatnya akun.
Mr. Dundar.
Pak Dundar.
Ya Shafi.
Ya Syafi'i.
Healing is only from you, my Lord.
Penyembuhan hanya dari Anda, Tuhanku.
Brother.
Adikku.
Brother, are you okay?
Saudaraku, kamu baik-baik saja?
I don't feel anything from the sting of my heart, brother.
Aku tidak merasakan apa pun dari sengatan hatiku, saudara.
My brother will pass. All will pass.
Saudaraku akan lulus, semua akan berlalu.
We will overcome them.
Kami akan mengatasinya.
How did I get so heedless?
Bagaimana saya bisa begitu lalai?
How did I do this to you, brother?
Bagaimana saya melakukan ini padamu, saudara?
I göktug ...
Saya Goktug ...
... let's look at the end of a job, not the end.
... mari kita lihat akhir pekerjaan, bukan akhir.
Look, it's finally beautiful.
Lihat, ini akhirnya indah.
We achieved.
Kami dicapai.
This is the important thing.
Ini yang penting.
If only...
Saya berharap ...
... I wish our mother was our father ...
... Saya berharap ibu kita adalah ayah kita ...
... brother had seen us shoulder to shoulder like this.
... saudara telah melihat kami bahu membahu seperti ini.
They didn't, brother.
Mereka tidak melakukannya, saudara.
They saw this a lot.
Mereka sering melihat ini.
Home us, our father ...
Rumah kami, ayah kami ...
... the Mongols burned us.
... bangsa Mongol membakar kita.
But you are not worried.
Tapi kamu tidak khawatir.
It will be beautiful beyond that.
Lebih indah dari itu.
How will it be brother?
Bagaimana saudara laki-lakinya?
How is it going to be?
Bagaimana itu akan terjadi?
I got into the blood of so many people.
Saya masuk ke dalam darah banyak orang.
I was cruel.
Saya kejam.
Does Osman Bey forgive me?
Apakah Osman Bey memaafkanku?
My Osman Bey is as merciful as he is fair.
Osman Bey saya berbelas kasihan seperti dia adil.
Stop it.
Hentikan itu.
Let the crowd at your head break.
Biarkan orang banyak di kepala Anda istirahat.
When we explain it, it will surely understand us.
Ketika kita menjelaskannya, itu pasti akan mengerti kita.
Balgay.
Balgay.
Balgay does not leave a dog.
Balgay tidak meninggalkan anjing.
I know it.
Saya tahu itu.
He will not digest it.
Dia tidak akan mencernanya.
Not Balgay ...
Bukan Balgay ...
... by removing nine swabs and the sentence coming over Mongolian ...
... dengan menghapus sembilan penyeka dan hukuman datang ke Mongolia ...
... I still don't give you, brother.
... Aku masih belum memberimu, saudara.
We forgot the wound from the longing for brotherhood.
Kami lupa luka dari kerinduan akan persaudaraan.
I'll go get you some ointment.
Aku akan mengambilkanmu salep.
Let's drive.
Ayo mengemudi.
My brother.
Saudaraku.
Hope.
Harapan.
Father...
Ayah ...
what happened here?
apa yang terjadi di sini
God...
Tuhan ...
... bless us from the evil of my mind, son.
... memberkati kita dari kejahatan pikiran saya, Nak.
Osman?
Osman?
How does he do that?
Bagaimana dia melakukannya?
Obviously...
Jelas ...
Samsa's alps ...
Alpen Samsa ...
... entered service.
... memasuki layanan.
How long does this go like this, Dad?
Berapa lama ini seperti ini, Ayah?
We have to stop Osman.
Kita harus menghentikan Osman.
Either we will stop Osman ...
Entah kita akan menghentikan Osman ...
...or...
... atau ...
Balgay's anger ...
Kemarahan Balgay ...
... will shoot us.
... akan menembak kita.
Osman.
Osman.
You were like this when you were little.
Anda seperti ini ketika Anda masih kecil.
Is somewhere aching or whining ...
Apakah di suatu tempat sakit atau merengek ...
... you would have been said to spoil.
... Anda akan dikatakan merusak.
The Mongolian dog took my mind.
Anjing Mongolia itu mengambil pikiran saya.
I hardly remember those days.
Saya hampir tidak ingat hari-hari itu.
I göktug ...
Saya Goktug ...
... you dismantled the shackles in your soul ...
... Anda membongkar belenggu dalam jiwa Anda ...
... nothing will happen to you informally.
... tidak ada yang akan terjadi pada Anda secara informal.
Is it good?
Apakah itu oke?
Good brother.
Saudara yang baik
I never reach.
Saya tidak pernah mencapai.
I'll tell you all.
Saya akan menceritakan semuanya.
Home us, our father, our obama ...
Rumah kami, ayah kami, obama kami ...
I will even tell you about the wars we made with wooden swords.
Saya bahkan akan bercerita tentang perang yang kami buat dengan pedang kayu.
I'll remind them all.
Saya akan mengingatkan mereka semua.
I took your hand ...
Saya mengambil tangan Anda ...
... I will not let it go again, brother.
... Aku tidak akan membiarkannya pergi lagi, saudara.
Thank you bro.
Terima kasih kawan
Thank you my brother.
Terima kasih saudaraku.
My brother.
Adikku.
So finally ...
Jadi akhirnya ...
... you did that too, Osman?
... kamu juga melakukannya, Osman?
Now...
Sekarang ...
... from Balgay's hand ...
... dari tangan Balgay ...
Who will save you?
Siapa yang akan menyelamatkanmu?
Who will save you from my hand Dundar Bey?
Siapa yang akan menyelamatkanmu dari tanganku Dundar Bey?
What is that?
Apa itu
Are you afraid that your master who kept his halves will be killed?
Apakah Anda takut tuanmu yang menyimpan setengahnya akan dibunuh?
Batur!
Batur!
Stop it, son.
Hentikan, nak.
He sealed his death warrant.
Dia menyegel surat kematiannya.
You will not find your hand in sister blood.
Anda tidak akan menemukan tangan Anda dalam darah saudara perempuan.
The honored blood of Atam Süleyman Şah ...
Darah terhormat Atam Süleyman Şah ...
.. if I don't buy from you ...
.. jika saya tidak membeli dari Anda ...
...me too...
... untukku ...
... Ertuğrul Gazi son Osman should not say.
... Ertuğrul Gazi putra Osman seharusnya tidak mengatakan.
Where is the daytime?
Di mana siang hari?
I got it in my brother's hands.
Saya mendapatkannya di tangan saudara saya.
What would they want from your brother?
Apa yang mereka inginkan dari saudaramu?
They asked for their trouble.
Mereka meminta masalah mereka.
Now it's your turn.
Sekarang giliranmu.
Ah...
Oh ...
Osman ah!
Osman ah!
Ah!
Ah!
Me with you...
Aku bersamamu ...
What am I gonna do?
Apa yang akan saya lakukan?
You sure you would.
Anda yakin akan melakukannya.
My father's coat ...
Mantel ayahku ...
... you sold it to Mongolian.
... Anda menjualnya ke Mongolia.
Then you were built on it.
Kemudian Anda dibangun di atasnya.
I did it for our obese.
Saya melakukannya untuk obesitas kita.
I did it for you.
Aku melakukannya untukmu.
Following you ...
Mengikuti kamu ...
... all the stout ...
... semua gemuk ...
... I did it to save your life. Don't you still understand?
... Aku melakukannya untuk menyelamatkan hidupmu, Apakah kamu masih tidak mengerti?
HE?
HE?
Your goodness, sink, Dundar.
Astaga, sink, Dundar.
If you cut us with pusat in your waist ...
Jika Anda memotong kami dengan pusat di pinggang Anda ...
... you would have a memory in your eyes.
... Anda akan memiliki memori di mata Anda.
But Dundar Bey, now you are nothing big in our eyes.
Tapi Dundar Bey, sekarang kau bukan hal besar di mata kami.
What about the state ...
Bagaimana dengan negara ...
... or the raven carrion.
... atau gagak gagak.
How many of our heroes died because of you.
Berapa banyak dari pahlawan kita yang mati karena kamu.
When will Osman's blood fall into your eyes?
Kapan darah Osman akan jatuh ke matamu?
When will it fill?
Kapan itu akan mengisi?
Martyrs they are martyrs.
Martir mereka adalah martir.
But people like you don't understand.
Tetapi orang-orang seperti Anda tidak mengerti.
They don't know Dündar Bey.
Mereka tidak tahu Dündar Bey.
Samsa Bey ...
Samsa Bey ...
... Mr. Bamsı ...
... Tn. Bamsi ...
how is this beylik?
bagaimana ini beylik?
How is this beylik?
Bagaimana beylik ini?
So much of Mongolian's death ...
Begitu banyak kematian Mongolia ...
... how are we going to pay?
... bagaimana kita akan membayar?
We will pay the price with the blood of our martyrs.
Kami akan membayar harganya dengan darah para martir kami.
This land conquered by my father ...
Tanah ini ditaklukkan oleh ayah saya ...
... we will not sacrifice those sold like you.
... kami tidak akan mengorbankan yang dijual seperti Anda.
Alps...
Alpen ...
...kill them all.
... bunuh mereka semua.
Do not force Demirci Bey.
Jangan paksa Demirci Bey.
I said do not force Demirci Bey.
Aku bilang jangan paksakan Demirci Bey.
I said do not force.
Saya bilang jangan paksa.
Storm...
Bora ...
... I would like Dündar Bey alive. Come on!
... Saya ingin Dündar Bey hidup. Ayo!
Thank you sir.
Terima kasih tuan
He's gone this way.
Dia pergi dengan cara ini.
Lets hurry up.
Ayo cepat.
Let's.
Ayo.
Mr. Alişar ...
Tuan Alişar ...
...you huh.
... kamu ya
You know you're coming from this side.
Anda tahu Anda berasal dari sisi ini.
Run Melik ...
Jalankan Melik ...
Osman, let Batur follow you.
Osman, biarkan Batur mengikutimu.
You will lose track of the stream there.
Anda akan kehilangan jejak arus di sana.
This is not a trail of Batur.
Ini bukan jejak Batur.
This is another.
Ini yang lain.
Who is it?
Siapa itu
Batur!
Batur!
Thank God we don't have a loss, sir.
Terima kasih Tuhan, kami tidak rugi, tuan.
Boran brother is after Dündar Bey.
Saudara Boran mengejar Dündar Bey.
Dumrul will fall into my hand sooner or later.
Dumrul akan jatuh ke tanganku cepat atau lambat.
Soon or later.
Cepat atau lambat.
Let's.
Ayo.
Hoo!
Hoo!
What is that?
Apa itu
My Sancak Bey has a horse-like state.
Sancak Bey saya memiliki kondisi seperti kuda.
Osman.
Osman.
What happened to Osman?
Apa yang terjadi pada Osman?
Osman...
Osman ...
attacked his headquarters.
menyerang markasnya.
He killed all his posts.
Dia membunuh semua jabatannya.
Now he's after my son.
Sekarang dia mengejar putraku.
Let me, let me track you with your sneakers.
Biarkan saya, biarkan saya melacak Anda dengan sepatu Anda.
Do you know what you're saying?
Apakah Anda tahu apa yang Anda katakan?
You've heard it. Let me ...
Anda sudah mendengarnya, biarkan saya ...
... I'll go after my son with your warnings.
... Aku akan mengejar putraku dengan peringatanmu.
Neutrals, go after Osman.
Netral, kejar Osman.
Dündar Bey will scout you.
Dündar Bey akan mengintai Anda.
Hurry up!
Cepat!
Balgay, Where is Balgay Gündüz? Why did you miss my nephew?
Balgay, Di mana Balgay Gündüz? Mengapa Anda merindukan keponakan saya?
What do you want from him?
Apa yang kamu inginkan darinya?
Genghis Khan's laws ...
Hukum Jenghis Khan ...
... he was the one who informed Geyhatu.
... dia adalah orang yang memberi tahu Geyhatu.
The end of who betrayed me ...
Akhir yang mengkhianati saya ...
Dundar Bey is death.
Dundar Bey adalah maut.
I am Osman.
Saya Osman.
Lets go!
Mari kita pergi!
Day, nephew.
Hari, keponakan.
I hope you are aware of the ringing you fell.
Saya harap Anda menyadari dering Anda jatuh.
Lift your head.
Angkat kepalamu.
You lift your head.
Anda mengangkat kepala Anda.
Answer me.
Jawab aku.
Why would you like the cruelty?
Mengapa Anda menyukai kekejaman itu?
For what?
Apa itu
We're scared, sir.
Kami takut, tuan.
Brave once ...
Berani sekali ...
... cowards die every day Şahin Bey.
... pengecut mati setiap hari Şahin Bey.
Beech gentlemen are always dignified.
Tuan-tuan Beech selalu bermartabat.
It will be upright.
Itu akan lurus.
Now...
Sekarang ...
... you are in good memory ...
... Anda berada dalam ingatan yang baik ...
... you can see well.
... kamu bisa melihat dengan baik.
The wrongdoing of the bees, whose reputation you have made,
Kesalahan lebah, yang reputasinya telah Anda buat,
... we got into their lair.
... kami masuk ke sarang mereka.
You fight us, dry fight ...
Anda melawan kami, pertarungan kering ...
... do you think he will fight raw?
... apakah kamu pikir dia akan bertarung mentah?
This fight is superstitious with Truth ...
Pertarungan ini takhayul dengan Kebenaran ...
is a fight between oppressed and oppressed.
adalah pertarungan antara yang tertindas dan yang tertindas.
Bondage traps set up in Turk are abundant.
Perangkap perbudakan yang didirikan di Turk berlimpah.
I will note that the Turkish will not surrender, sentence cihana.
Saya akan perhatikan bahwa orang Turki tidak akan menyerah, kalimat cihana.
I swear on my black pus ...
Saya bersumpah pada nanah hitam saya ...
I will flag the sky and flag the sun.
Saya akan mengibarkan langit dan mengibarkan matahari.
My damn wasted cruel ...
Sialan saya sia-sia kejam ...
... there will be hope for the oppressed.
... akan ada harapan bagi yang tertindas.
Allahu akbar!
Allahu akbar!
I Uthman ...
Saya Utsman ...
what are we gonna do?
apa yang akan kita lakukan
Let them go to the place.
Biarkan mereka pergi ke tempat itu.
... if you come across this one more time ...
... jika Anda menemukan ini sekali lagi ...
... then I can forgive you.
... maka aku bisa memaafkanmu.
Bey.
Bey.
Balgay comes here.
Balgay datang ke sini.
Crowds.
Orang banyak.
We prepared such a welcome for him.
Kami menyiapkan sambutan untuknya.
To see.
Untuk melihat.
Let's.
Ayo.
What do you want, Alişar from me?
Apa yang kamu inginkan, Alişar dari saya?
I saved you from Osman.
Saya menyelamatkan Anda dari Osman.
Is not it enough?
Bukankah itu cukup?
You have no judgment on this land.
Anda tidak memiliki penilaian atas tanah ini.
Especially there is no one on me, Alişar.
Terutama tidak ada orang di saya, Alişar.
Wow Wow wow.
Wow wow wow.
So I have no judgment?
Jadi saya tidak punya penilaian?
In this land ...
Di negeri ini ...
... do you think your father has a judgment?
... apakah menurutmu ayahmu memiliki penilaian?
Don't make me laugh.
Jangan membuatku tertawa.
First of all, your father's stardom ...
Pertama-tama, ketenaran ayahmu ...
... know that you owe your mother ...
... tahu bahwa kamu berutang ibumu ...
... speak like that.
... bicara seperti itu.
How about you?
Bagaimana dengan anda
If Anan didn't sell his soul to Balgay ...
Jika Anan tidak menjual jiwanya ke Balgay ...
... your father only dreamed of starboard.
... Ayahmu hanya memimpikan kanan.
You lie.
Kamu berbohong
Anan to save you from Osman's hand ...
Anan untuk menyelamatkanmu dari tangan Osman ...
... went first and sold Bala Hatun.
... pergi dulu dan menjual Bala Hatun.
Then Gündüz Bey to save your father.
Kemudian Gündüz Bey untuk menyelamatkan ayahmu.
Gündüz Bey, who told Geyhatu about the laws of Cengiz, lied.
Gündüz Bey, yang memberi tahu Geyhatu tentang hukum Cengiz, berbohong.
How do you know them?
Bagaimana Anda mengenal mereka?
Don't you know my ear is a hole?
Apakah kamu tidak tahu telingaku lubang?
I have eyes and ears everywhere.
Saya memiliki mata dan telinga di mana-mana.
Still haven't learned?
Masih belum belajar?
As for your father ...
Adapun ayahmu ...
... for the gentleman of Gündüz Bey oba ...
... untuk pria Gündüz Bey oba ...
... was brave enough to sacrifice himself.
... cukup berani untuk mengorbankan dirinya sendiri.
He didn't say Balgay single.
Dia tidak mengatakan Balgay lajang.
Your father did not gamble.
Ayahmu tidak bertaruh.
However, your dad ...
Namun, ayahmu ...
... oh that poor ...
... oh itu miskin ...
... your cowardly father.
... ayah pengecutmu.
I came here friendly.
Saya datang ke sini ramah.
What do you want, Alişar from me?
Apa yang kamu inginkan, Alişar dari saya?
Where is Bala Hatun?
Dimanakah Bala Hatun?
Say your place, let's get paid.
Katakan tempat Anda, mari kita dibayar.
Go to Oban.
Pergi ke Oban.
Witness what I say is truth.
Saksikan apa yang saya katakan adalah kebenaran.
I ask for the last time.
Saya meminta yang terakhir kali.
Where is Bala Hatun?
Dimanakah Bala Hatun?
I don't know where Bala Hatun is.
Saya tidak tahu di mana Bala Hatun berada.
I don't owe you either.
Aku juga tidak berhutang budi padamu.
If you are a son ...
Jika Anda seorang putra ...
... die right.
... mati saja.
On my way ...
Dalam perjalanan ...
Osman became an enemy to your father.
Osman menjadi musuh ayahmu.
Thanks to you ...
Terima kasih untukmu ...
Dundar will be an enemy to Osman.
Dundar akan menjadi musuh bagi Osman.
They will shed each other's blood.
Mereka akan saling menumpahkan darah.
Then Geyhatu ...
Lalu Geyhatu ...
... Balgay's account ...
... akun Balgay ...
... to see.
... untuk melihat.
All of my enemies ...
Semua musuhku ...
... I will break each other.
... Aku akan saling menghancurkan.
Bastard!
Inglourious!
Let it lie down.
Biarkan berbaring.
Leave this push carcass close to the oba in the morning.
Biarkan bangkai dorong ini dekat dengan oba di pagi hari.
Let it be watered with sister blood ...
Biarkan itu disiram dengan darah saudara perempuan ...
... my sanjid principal.
... Kepala sekolah saya.
Stop, you're stuck.
Berhenti, kamu mandek.
Is there any water, brother?
Apakah ada air, saudara?
You want your brother to pierce the mountains and bring water.
Anda ingin saudara Anda menembus gunung dan membawa air.
You were like this when you were young, did you want something ...
Anda seperti ini ketika Anda masih muda, apakah Anda menginginkan sesuatu ...
... innocent innocent brother who narrows his eyes ...
... Saudara yang tidak bersalah tidak bersalah yang menyipitkan matanya ...
Fool.
Menipu.
Erlik Han ...
Erlik Han ...
Send me your anger from the spirits!
Kirimkan aku kemarahanmu dari roh!
...you...
... Anda ...
... I said to meet Osman.
... Aku berkata untuk menemui Osman.
It turns out ...
Ternyata ...
... I said you are saturated with black blood.
... Saya katakan Anda jenuh dengan darah hitam.
I said to the blue sky full of the breath of death.
Saya berkata kepada langit biru yang penuh dengan nafas kematian.
Erlik Han ...
Erlik Han ...
... or take my soul ...
... atau ambil jiwaku ...
... or me ...
... atau aku ...
... give Osman.
... berikan Osman.
Get up.
Bangun.
While Osman obama was pressing ...
Sementara Osman obama menekan ...
what the hell do you do?
apa yang kamu lakukan
Cerkutay.
Cerkutay.
What the hell would you do Cerkutay?
Apa yang akan kamu lakukan Cerkutay?
They were very crowded, Balgay.
Mereka sangat ramai, Balgay.
Samsa's alps also joined him.
Alpen Samsa juga bergabung dengannya.
Erlik Han ...
Erlik Han ...
... give me Osman.
... beri aku Osman.
Erlik Han!
Erlik Han!
Bala.
Bala.
I was going to ask how are you
Aku akan bertanya apa kabar
But I understood when I saw Sofia.
Tetapi saya mengerti ketika saya melihat Sofia.
You are good.
Kamu baik
You have a problem.
Anda punya masalah.
You will not tell.
Anda tidak akan memberitahu.
Say, well.
Katakan, baik.
Let me level the mountains.
Biarkan saya naik gunung.
Let's not say surviving these days, except surviving.
Jangan katakan bertahan hidup hari ini, kecuali bertahan hidup.
Waits for the bud. Let me help.
Tunggu tunasnya. Biarkan saya membantu.
You're thirsty.
Anda haus.
You're gone.
Kau pergi.
You ignore me.
Kamu abaikan aku.
This is not the case, Bala.
Ini tidak terjadi, Bala.
What is possible to ignore you?
Apa yang mungkin untuk mengabaikan Anda?
Let me leave me for a while.
Biarkan aku meninggalkanku sebentar.
Inform the thesis of Konya.
Informasikan tesis Konya.
New posts come.
Posting baru datang.
If you are clumsy like you ...
Jika Anda kikuk seperti Anda ...
... this time I won't leave it to Osman ...
... kali ini aku tidak akan menyerahkannya pada Osman ...
... I kill with my own hands.
... Saya bunuh dengan tangan saya sendiri.
Did Sogut's air soften you too, Kongar?
Apakah udara Sogut juga melembutkanmu, Kongar?
Samsa ...
Samsa ...
... at the feet of my horse.
... di kaki kudaku.
At the last moment Osman and his alps grew up, Commander Balgay.
Pada saat terakhir Osman dan pasukannya tumbuh, Komandan Balgay.
Cut!
Cut!
You couldn't handle a goatherd.
Anda tidak bisa menangani kambing gembala.
They were very crowded, Commander Balgay.
Mereka sangat ramai, Komandan Balgay.
We didn't even understand where they came from.
Kami bahkan tidak mengerti dari mana mereka berasal.
Do not look for the incompetence again.
Jangan mencari ketidakmampuan lagi.
Do not!
Tidak!
How did you get rid of your hands?
Bagaimana Anda menyingkirkan tangan Anda?
You know, Commander Balgay ...
Anda tahu, Komandan Balgay ...
... the chain that will hold me has not been invented yet.
... rantai yang akan menahan saya belum ditemukan.
Are their locations clear?
Apakah lokasi mereka jelas?
Their measures are harsh.
Tindakan mereka keras.
They took me to Sofia separately.
Mereka membawa saya ke Sofia secara terpisah.
The whole forest became a refuge for them.
Seluruh hutan menjadi tempat perlindungan bagi mereka.
It is impossible to find Osman by searching.
Tidak mungkin menemukan Osman dengan mencari.
Commander Balgay, Alişar came.
Komandan Balgay, Alişar datang.
Get on the floor.
Dapatkan di lantai.
Go prepare for you.
Bersiaplah untuk Anda.
We will take the life of Osman tomorrow.
Kami akan mengambil kehidupan Osman besok.
No it is put ...
Tidak diletakkan ...
...what are you doing here?
Apa yang kamu lakukan disini
Where is Kongar?
Dimanakah Kongar?
Won't you hear my skin?
Anda tidak akan mendengar kulit saya?
Beyim Kongar fled.
Beyim Kongar melarikan diri.
What do you mean?
Apa maksudmu
Didn't I say open your eyes?
Bukankah sudah kubilang buka matamu?
Didn't I?
Bukan begitu?
Sir sir ...
Pak tuan ...
... asked for water.
... meminta air.
When filling the bowl with water ...
Saat mengisi mangkuk dengan air ...
... hit me from behind.
... pukul aku dari belakang.
Didn't you tie him somewhere after we left?
Tidakkah kamu mengikatnya di suatu tempat setelah kita pergi?
Didn't you tie up?
Apakah kamu tidak mengikat?
I did not connect, sir.
Saya tidak terhubung, Pak.
Get up!
Bangun!
You are destroyed in duty, but not in front of me.
Anda hancur dalam tugas, tetapi tidak di depan saya.
Kill me, sir.
Bunuh aku, tuan.
Kill.
Membunuh.
Why didn't you tie Kongar?
Kenapa kamu tidak mengikat Kongar?
Why not take your precaution?
Mengapa tidak mengambil tindakan pencegahan Anda?
I can't say thank you sir.
Saya tidak bisa mengucapkan terima kasih, Pak.
I'm looking.
Saya sedang mencari
What can you say, Konur?
Apa yang bisa Anda katakan, Konur?
What can you not say?
Apa yang tidak bisa Anda katakan?
You will snatch me, Comrade Murderer.
Anda akan menangkap saya, Kamerad Pembunuh.
Go away, let me see you.
Pergi, biarkan aku melihatmu.
I dont go.
Aku harus pergi.
I don't go anywhere.
Saya tidak pergi kemana-mana.
Let my heart be removed from my chest, yet I will not leave your bottom.
Biarkan hatiku dilepas dari dadaku, namun aku tidak akan meninggalkan pantatmu.
Then why didn't you tie Kongar?
Lalu mengapa kamu tidak mengikat Kongar?
For what?
Apa itu
Kong ...
Kong ...
... my lost brother is Göktuğ.
... saudara saya yang hilang adalah Göktuğ.
What news did you bring to me from Konda?
Berita apa yang kamu bawakan dari Konda?
I couldn't get to Geyhatu.
Saya tidak bisa sampai ke Geyhatu.
But I heard everything spoken in the palace.
Tetapi saya mendengar semuanya berbicara di istana.
Talk.
Talk.
He heard that Geyhatu Osman had killed his son Köni.
Dia mendengar bahwa Geyhatu Osman telah membunuh putranya Köni.
He went crazy.
Dia menjadi gila.
He brought the gold of the palace on him.
Dia membawa emas istana padanya.
Not getting his anger ...
Tidak mendapatkan amarahnya ...
... the sultan is said to have killed one of his princes.
... Sultan dikatakan telah membunuh salah satu pangerannya.
However, he does not see Osman's account ...
Namun, dia tidak melihat akun Osman ...
... if you don't take the laws away ...
... jika Anda tidak mengambil hukum ...
... Geyhatu the ...
... Geyhatu yang ...
... it is said that this will ask you to account.
... Dikatakan bahwa ini akan meminta Anda untuk bertanggung jawab.
He sent a scout troop to find Osman.
Dia mengirim pasukan pengintai untuk menemukan Osman.
They will come here at thesis time.
Mereka akan datang ke sini pada waktu tesis.
The Geyhatu ...
The Geyhatu ...
doesn't he trust me?
bukankah dia percaya padaku?
There is a multi-state palace in Balgay who thinks that Genghis Khan has taken the laws for yourself.
Ada sebuah istana multi-negara di Balgay yang berpikir bahwa Jenghis Khan telah mengambil sendiri hukumnya.
Not that...
Namun ...
... gossip is not cut back.
... gosip tidak berkurang.
What does he think?
Apa yang dia pikirkan?
...I do not know.
... Saya tidak tahu.
Cut!
Cut!
Protect yourself from the wrath of Geyhatu, Balgay.
Lindungi diri Anda dari murka Geyhatu, Balgay.
I have come a long way now.
Saya telah datang jauh sekarang.
If you let me ...
Jika Anda membiarkan saya ...
... if you don't have a command ...
... jika Anda tidak memiliki perintah ...
I want to rest.
Saya ingin istirahat.
I have important jobs tomorrow.
Saya memiliki pekerjaan penting besok.
When I return ...
Ketika saya kembali ...
... I will have new orders for you.
... Saya akan memiliki pesanan baru untuk Anda.
I heard that he gave the Sanjak principality to Dundar Bey.
Saya mendengar bahwa dia memberikan kerajaan Sanjak kepada Dundar Bey.
Until I'm done with him.
Sampai aku selesai dengannya.
Go.
Go.
Thank God God has forgiven you.
Terima kasih Tuhan, Tuhan telah mengampuni Anda.
Thank you brother.
Terima kasih saudara
Day.
Siang hari.
Aunt.
Bibi.
I Aisha ...
Saya Aisha ...
What are you doing here?
Apa yang kamu lakukan disini
How did you come?
Bagaimana kamu datang?
Osman brought it.
Osman membawanya.
I couldn't stop there.
Saya tidak bisa berhenti di situ.
What did they do to you during the day?
Apa yang mereka lakukan pada Anda di siang hari?
Whatever they did, they did.
Apa pun yang mereka lakukan, mereka lakukan.
My brother pulled me out of this cender.
Adikku menarikku keluar dari kas ini.
Informal after that ...
Informal setelah itu ...
... we will look together.
... kita akan melihat bersama.
May Allah be pleased with you, Osman.
Semoga Allah senang dengan Anda, Osman.
God gives shoulder in this war ...
Tuhan memberi bahu dalam perang ini ...
... the chick ...
... anak ayam ...
... the er ...
... er yang ...
... bless you from many valiant brothers.
... memberkatimu dari banyak saudara yang gagah berani.
Do I ever protect my brother in the hands of those bastards?
Apakah saya pernah melindungi saudara saya di tangan para bajingan itu?
Welcome, Ayşe Hatun.
Selamat datang, Ayse Hatun.
We're [I'm] glad to be here.
Kami menemukannya bagus.
May Allah heal at thesis time Gündüz Bey.
Semoga Allah menyembuhkan pada saat tesis Gündüz Bey.
Thank you.
Terima kasih.
Mr. Osman...
Osman Bey ...
... come a little.
... datang sedikit.
I have something to say to you.
Aku ingin mengatakan sesuatu padamu.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Jangan khawatir, aku baik-baik saja.
Thank god.
Syukurlah.
Let me say without a shortcut.
Biar saya katakan tanpa jalan pintas.
Understand, Osman Bey.
Pahami, Osman Bey.
Our companionship will always continue in war.
Persahabatan kita akan selalu berlanjut dalam perang.
You should not expect anything beyond me.
Anda seharusnya tidak mengharapkan apa pun di luar saya.
I won't leave without saying why, Bala.
Saya tidak akan pergi tanpa mengatakan alasannya, Bala.
I was raised for these days.
Saya dibesarkan untuk hari ini.
My duty is to stand next to my father ...
Tugas saya adalah berdiri di samping ayah saya ...
... it's time to do my part.
... saatnya untuk melakukan bagian saya.
I realized that love is not my fee.
Saya menyadari bahwa cinta bukanlah bayaran saya.
What did you say, Bala?
Apa yang kamu katakan, Bala?
There is something else.
Ada sesuatu yang lain.
There is something else, but you keep it.
Ada sesuatu yang lain, tetapi Anda menyimpannya.
This is beyond.
Ini di luar.
Have a look at another chick.
Lihatlah cewek lain.
There is no good for you Osman Bey.
Tidak ada gunanya bagimu Osman Bey.
Pususim is always at your disposal.
Pususim selalu siap membantu Anda.
God let him open the way.
Semoga Allah menjelaskan jalannya.
Where are my dads?
Di mana ayah saya?
Don't do Vesvese, Aygül. Set up the table. Now comes your father.
Jangan lakukan Vesvese, Aygül. Mengatur meja. Sekarang datang ayahmu.
Father.
Ayah.
Bey.
Bey.
What is this state, sir?
Keadaan apa ini, tuan?
Osman...
Osman ...
... raided Osman Balgay's headquarters.
... menyerbu markas Osman Balgay.
He wanted to kill me with Batur.
Dia ingin membunuhku dengan Batur.
He chopped our Alps.
Dia memotong Pegunungan Alpen kami.
Where is Batur Dündar Bey?
Di mana Batur Dündar Bey?
He went after Osman Batur.
Dia mengejar Osman Batur.
With us, we searched everywhere with the guards, but we could not find a trace.
Bersama kami, kami mencari di mana-mana dengan penjaga, tetapi kami tidak dapat menemukan jejak.
Son.
Anak saya.
My Osman obviously went to get his brother.
Osman saya jelas pergi untuk mendapatkan saudaranya.
You will become the starboard of ite, who kidnapped Gündüz Bey and killed his alps ...
Anda akan menjadi kanan kanan, yang menculik Gündüz Bey dan membunuh Alpen-nya ...
... then you ask the account of the brother blood from Osman.
... maka Anda bertanya akun darah saudara dari Osman.
Enough!
Cukup!
Get out of our hat, chick!
Keluar dari topi kami, cewek!
When was Otağ yours, babe?
Kapan Otağ milikmu, sayang?
Selcan Hatun ...
Selcan Hatun ...
... go away before I have an accident.
... pergi sebelum saya mengalami kecelakaan.
Evvel Bala Hatun is now Day ...
Evvel Bala Hatun sekarang adalah Hari ...
Dundar has a big hole in his room.
Dundar memiliki lubang besar di kamarnya.
Do you stay behind the felt of the couch?
Apakah Anda tetap berada di balik nuansa sofa?
Can you put on a wing and go to Balgay's ear?
Bisakah Anda mengenakan sayap dan pergi ke telinga Balgay?
What do you mean?
Apa maksudmu
Take it out of your mouth.
Keluarkan itu dari mulutmu.
What I mean is obvious.
Yang saya maksud sudah jelas.
I came to say that Ayşe Hatun is not in her tent.
Saya datang untuk mengatakan bahwa Ayşe Hatun tidak ada di tendanya.
Now I realized that my Osman took Ayşe Hatun with Gündüz.
Sekarang saya menyadari bahwa Osman saya membawa Ayşe Hatun dengan Gündüz.
The world of discovery.
Dunia penemuan.
Nice calculation of the blood of our alps ...
Perhitungan yang bagus dari darah Alpen kami ...
... not from Osman ...
... bukan dari Osman ...
... the day we will ask you comes step by step.
... hari kami akan meminta Anda datang langkah demi langkah.
You have no heart to hit me.
Anda tidak tega memukul saya.
Babe ...
Sayang ...
... chick get out of here.
... cewek keluar dari sini.
Get out!
Keluar!
Obama has ...
Obama memiliki ...
... at our ceremony.
... di upacara kami.
Dundar will not let the rest go, the rest is gone.
Dundar tidak akan membiarkan sisanya pergi, sisanya hilang.
The outgoing and the remaining are waiting on the watch.
Yang keluar dan sisanya sedang menunggu di arloji.
Saltuk ...
Saltuk ...
... alps, get ready for the thesis.
... alps, bersiap-siap untuk tesis.
We will set out to search for Batur Bey.
Kami akan berangkat untuk mencari Batur Bey.
Before Osman died ...
Sebelum Osman meninggal ...
... there is no return to oba.
... tidak ada kembali ke oba.
This is yours, sir.
Ini milikmu, tuan.
I Usman.
Aku Usman.
Come on, Osman.
Ayo, Osman.
You're coming.
Anda datang.
I Uthman ...
Saya Utsman ...
What is his heart ...
Apa hatinya ...
Are you betrayed?
Apakah Anda dikhianati?
Or is he an opponent?
Atau dia lawan?
What an opponent breaks my waist.
Apa yang lawan hancurkan pinggangku.
What betrayal narrows deep.
Pengkhianatan apa yang menyempit.
Bamsı Bey is in my heart.
Bamsı Bey ada di hatiku.
My heart.
Hatiku.
I Uthman ...
Saya Utsman ...
... of Sheikh Edebali ...
... dari Sheikh Edebali ...
... if it was his consent ...
... jika itu persetujuannya ...
... you don't worry.
... kamu tidak khawatir.
He is a literary person.
Dia adalah orang sastra.
Obviously...
Jelas ...
Waiting for your vat, Osman.
Menunggu tongmu, Osman.
It is not the literary that led me to gamma.
Bukan sastra yang membawa saya ke gamma.
Bala is.
Bala.
Extinguished heart fire.
Api jantung padam.
He said I don't want you.
Dia bilang aku tidak menginginkanmu.
First of all, his father saw him missing ...
Pertama-tama, ayahnya melihatnya hilang ...
... now her daughter ...
... sekarang putrinya ...
now he despises the girl.
sekarang dia membenci gadis itu.
I Uthman ...
Saya Utsman ...
... where did he come from?
... dari mana asalnya?
You, you don't make the final judgment.
Anda, Anda tidak membuat keputusan akhir.
The verdict is not me ...
Putusan itu bukan aku ...
... He gave it to me, Bamsı Bey.
... Dia memberikannya kepadaku, Bamsı Bey.
In fact, it is not wrong.
Padahal, itu tidak salah.
We're on a road that we don't know what will happen tomorrow.
Kami berada di jalan yang kami tidak tahu apa yang akan terjadi besok.
So...
Jadi ...
... so walking with me was heavy for him.
... jadi berjalan denganku sangat berat baginya.
It came heavy.
Itu datang berat.
Son ...
Anak ...
... I know Bala girl.
... Aku kenal gadis Bala.
I know my daughter Bala.
Saya tahu putri saya Bala.
What is he worrying about tomorrow ...
Apa yang dia khawatirkan tentang besok ...
nor escapes difficulty.
atau lolos dari kesulitan.
Son, you are the clear water of that heart river ...
Nak, kau adalah air jernih dari sungai hati itu ...
... do not mess with occasions.
... jangan main-main dengan kesempatan.
Heart in love ...
Jatuh cinta ...
his heart carries patience.
hatinya membawa kesabaran.
Love business is troublesome.
Bisnis cinta itu merepotkan.
I Usman, both ...
Aku Usman, baik ...
... it seems to me that ...
... Sepertinya saya bahwa ...
... there is a job in this.
... ada pekerjaan dalam hal ini.
Come out soon.
Segera keluar.
Vote vote, Osman.
Vote vote, Osman.
Waiting is a fate for his lover, Osman.
Menunggu adalah takdir bagi kekasihnya, Osman.
Joyful...
Anda ...
... you can patience.
... kamu bisa sabar.
Patience, boy.
Sabar, nak.
My fault.
Karena aku.
Alp is put ...
Alp diletakkan ...
...Where are you?
dimana kamu
Where have I been, Samsa Sergeant?
Di mana aku berada, Sersan Samsa?
Say, well.
Katakan, baik.
Where was I?
Di mana saya?
It's my brother.
Ini saudaraku.
Where have I been, Samsa Sergeant?
Di mana aku berada, Sersan Samsa?
You did whatever you need.
Anda melakukan apa pun yang Anda butuhkan.
Even if you were offended by your own brother, I wouldn't forgive you.
Bahkan jika kamu tersinggung oleh saudaramu sendiri, aku tidak akan memaafkanmu.
This is a brother.
Ini adalah saudara laki-laki.
My brother Ala Börü ...
Saudaraku Ala Börü ...
... I gave the city in the Mongolian raid.
... Saya memberikan kota dalam serangan Mongolia.
In front of my eyes.
Di depan mataku.
If he was the only survivor, he was mankurt.
Jika dia adalah satu-satunya yang selamat, dia adalah mankurt
Wouldn't I turn it into the essence of hitting with those hands?
Tidakkah saya mengubahnya menjadi inti dari memukul dengan tangan itu?
As long as I knew you were breathing.
Selama aku tahu kamu bernafas.
Ala Börü is now right.
Ala Börü sekarang benar.
It's for me ...
Ini untukku ...
... I can't help praying.
... Aku tidak bisa berhenti berdoa.
But your income.
Tapi penghasilanmu.
Take care of your brother.
Jaga saudaramu.
We are with you.
Kami bersamamu.
Believe me, Samsa Bey.
Percayalah, Samsa Bey.
He won't believe me.
Dia tidak akan percaya padaku.
Thread ...
Thread ...
... why can't he believe you?
... kenapa dia tidak bisa percaya padamu?
Would he ever hurt you if he did not believe me?
Apakah dia akan pernah menyakitimu jika dia tidak percaya padaku?
You shouldn't worry, I am.
Anda tidak perlu khawatir, saya.
Göktuğ is a valiant mother ...
Göktuğ adalah seorang ibu yang gagah berani ...
obviously the son of a well-established father.
jelas putra seorang ayah yang mapan.
There is also mercy in his heart.
Ada juga belas kasihan di hatinya.
As long as that mercy is there ...
Selama belas kasihan itu ada ...
... there will be hope in us.
... akan ada harapan di dalam kita.
May you exist, Samsa Sergeant.
Semoga Anda ada, Samsa Sersan.
May you exist.
Semoga Anda ada.
Where are the neuters located?
Di mana posisi netral?
They are located right where you say, in the border of Inegol Tekfurlık.
Mereka terletak tepat di mana Anda mengatakan, di perbatasan Inegol Tekfurlık.
Where is our route?
Di mana rute kami?
Here.
Di sini.
The wolves crossed the hill ...
Serigala menyeberangi bukit ...
... we will reach the border.
... kita akan mencapai perbatasan.
Which route did the soldiers in Serhat pass?
Rute mana yang dilewati para prajurit di Serhat?
They passed here.
Mereka lewat di sini.
The other way is already long ...
Cara lain sudah lama ...
... and he's uncanny.
... dan dia luar biasa.
So we too ...
Jadi kita juga ...
... we will go over the wolves' hill.
... kita akan pergi ke bukit serigala.
With your mind as a bird ...
Dengan pikiranmu seperti burung ...
... you set a trap for me, Osman.
... Anda membuat jebakan untuk saya, Osman.
This time...
Kali ini ...
... you won't get rid of my paw.
... kamu tidak akan menyingkirkan kakiku.
I told Yannez that I was going to throw the trap into the Inegol border.
Saya mengatakan kepada Yannez bahwa saya akan melemparkan perangkap ke perbatasan Inegol.
Not that...
Namun ...
... warfare is cheating.
... peperangan itu curang.
We will not set the trap there.
Kami tidak akan mengatur jebakan di sana.
Full ...
Penuh ...
... we will install it on top of wolves.
... kita akan menginstalnya di atas serigala.
Balgay's headquarters ...
Markas Balgay ...
... a distance from here.
... jauh dari sini.
The ambush will never expect it to come from here.
Penyergapan tidak akan pernah mengharapkannya datang dari sini.
We will catch unprepared.
Kami akan menangkap tidak siap.
If Yannez said the ambush ...
Jika Yannez mengatakan serangan itu ...
... they have already prepared.
... mereka sudah siap.
Some of the Mongolian warpers have already crossed the hill of wolves and reached the border.
Beberapa warol Mongolia telah melintasi bukit serigala dan mencapai perbatasan.
Son, we'd say we'd take their heads off the road.
Nak, kita katakan kita akan mengambil kepala mereka dari jalan.
Bamsı Bey is the unity bait that I allowed to pass.
Bamsı Bey adalah umpan persatuan yang diizinkan untuk saya lewati.
Balgay will use that road as they pass that road safely.
Balgay akan menggunakan jalan itu saat mereka melewati jalan itu dengan aman.
At that time...
Lalu ...
... part of the shroud ...
... bagian dari kain kafan ...
... now waits for us in the Inegol border.
... sekarang menunggu kita di perbatasan Inegol.
Because of that, we will be divided into two.
Karena itu, kita akan dibagi menjadi dua.
Samsa Bey, you and your alps ...
Samsa Bey, Anda dan Alpen Anda ...
... where Mongolian soldiers are waiting for us ...
... di mana tentara Mongolia sedang menunggu kita ...
... you will go to Inegol border.
... Anda akan pergi ke perbatasan Inegol.
They waited a lot for us.
Mereka menunggu kami.
... you can fill their heads with their sculptures.
... Anda dapat mengisi kepala mereka dengan patung-patung mereka.
Don't bury their bodies in their lair.
Jangan mengubur tubuh mereka di sarang mereka.
Thank you.
Terima kasih.
Selcan Hatun ...
Selcan Hatun ...
What's up.
Tidak.
You fired from the room before ...
Anda dipecat dari kamar sebelum ...
... do you intend to fire it now?
... apakah kamu berniat memecatnya sekarang?
You will help Selcan Hatun.
Anda akan membantu Selcan Hatun.
I'll help.
Saya akan membantu
You have equalized each thing, Zöhre.
Anda telah menyamakan setiap hal, Zöhre.
What am I going to do to you?
Apa yang akan saya lakukan padamu?
My Batur still hasn't arrived.
Batur saya masih belum tiba.
Osman meant it.
Osman bersungguh-sungguh.
He doesn't leave his life.
Dia tidak meninggalkan hidupnya.
Let the news go crazy.
Biarkan berita itu menjadi gila.
He listens to you.
Dia mendengarkanmu.
Well! Enough informal.
Yah! Cukup informal.
Osman, you howling Osman.
Osman, kau melolong Osman.
Thinking about your own before ...
Memikirkan milikmu sendiri sebelum ...
... speak like that.
... bicara seperti itu.
You still say Osman.
Anda masih mengatakan Osman.
You couldn't see what that madman went.
Anda tidak bisa melihat apa yang dilakukan orang gila itu.
What did he do?
Apa yang dia lakukan?
What did Osman do?
Apa yang dilakukan Osman?
Even if you shed your own.
Bahkan jika kamu menumpahkan milikmu sendiri.
Previously Bala then Gündüz is now Batur.
Sebelumnya Bala maka Gündüz sekarang Batur.
Go on, let someone else let your news out.
Ayo, biarkan orang lain mengeluarkan berita Anda.
Obviously your hand is long.
Jelas tangan Anda panjang.
You will let me know, babe.
Anda akan memberi tahu saya, sayang.
If anything happens to my Batur ...
Jika sesuatu terjadi pada Batur saya ...
then you see Zöhre.
maka Anda melihat Zöhre.
Our Batur Bey.
Batur Bey kami.
They chopped our Batur Bey.
Mereka memotong Batur Bey kami.
Batur.
Batur.
Batur!
Batur!
What are you looking at?
Apa yang kamu lihat
Let's lift it.
Mari kita angkat.
Healing come on to the house.
Penyembuhan datang ke rumah.
It is useful, right?
Ini berguna, bukan?
Is it heavy?
Apakah berat?
Where is his wound?
Dimana lukanya?
Her mother makes her mother better.
Ibunya membuat ibunya lebih baik.
My lamb, my batur.
Anak domba saya, sifat saya.
Where is the wound, my child?
Di mana lukanya, anak saya?
My Batur My Batur.
Batur saya Batur saya.
Batur.
Batur.
Baby.
Baby.
Her mother will do it well.
Ibunya akan melakukannya dengan baik.
Her mother is a healer.
Ibunya adalah tabib.
Mother, Batu ...
Ibu, Batu ...
Batur lamb, baby.
Batur domba, sayang.
Open your eyes baby, Yavrum Batur.
Buka matamu, Yavrum Batur.
Open your eyes, lamb.
Buka matamu, domba.
Zöhre ...
Zöhre ...
... Batur is gone.
... Batur hilang.
He's dead.
Dia sudah mati.
No.
Tidak ada.
No Batur.
Tidak Batur.
Lamb open your eyes lamb.
Domba buka matamu, domba.
Let them see that sky open your lamb.
Biarkan mereka melihat langit membuka domba Anda.
Batur.
Batur.
Batur baby.
Batur sayang.
Baby baby.
Sayang sayang
Batur.
Batur.
Baby, baby.
Bayi, bayi.
Oh my baby, I'm Batur.
Oh sayangku, aku Batur.
My lamb.
domba saya.
They had my mince, Dundar.
Mereka punya cincang saya, Dundar.
They chopped my puppy.
Mereka memotong anak anjing saya.
Brother!
Adikku!
Big brother open your eyes, big brother.
Kakak membuka matamu, kakak.
Open your eyes.
Buka matamu.
They had my mince, Dundar.
Mereka punya cincang saya, Dundar.
They chopped on my lamb.
Mereka memotong domba saya.
Vote!
Vote!
Open your eyes, brother.
Buka matamu, saudara.
Batur.
Batur.
Son.
Anak saya.
I Baturina.
Aku Baturina.
My son open your eyes.
Anakku membuka matamu.
Look at your hungry son eyes. Your father came, son.
Lihatlah mata anakmu yang lapar. Ayahmu datang, nak.
Come on let's open your eyes, we have more work, my Batur.
Ayo, mari kita buka mata Anda, kita memiliki lebih banyak pekerjaan, Batur saya.
Come on, son.
Ayo, nak.
My son open your eyes, Batur.
Anakku membuka matamu, Batur.
Big brother open your eyes, big brother.
Kakak membuka matamu, kakak.
Batur.
Batur.
You burned yourself.
Kamu membakar dirimu sendiri.
Osman...
Osman ...
Osman made this treachery to my son.
Osman membuat pengkhianatan ini untuk putraku.
My son open your eyes.
Anakku membuka matamu.
Alps...
Alpen ...
... I alps ...
... Saya alps ...
... my alps, everyone is out of oba.
... Alpen saya, semua orang kehabisan oba.
Everywhere will be sought.
Di mana-mana akan dicari.
Everyone is out of oba.
Semua orang kehabisan oba.
Oh Osman!
Oh Osman!
Osman will not stay with you.
Osman tidak akan tinggal bersamamu.
Will not.
tidak akan.
I will ask you for the account of my son you murdered.
Saya akan meminta akun anak saya yang Anda bunuh.
I will ask Allah is my witness that I will ask you.
Saya akan bertanya kepada Allah adalah saksi saya bahwa saya akan bertanya kepada Anda.
I will ask you, I will ask you.
Aku akan bertanya padamu, aku akan bertanya padamu.
Oh my Batur!
Ya ampun!
Let's!
Ayo!
Come on, everyone is on the horse!
Ayo, semua orang di atas kuda!
Brother!
Adikku!
Kademsiz!
Kademsiz!
Mother.
Rumah.
Go stepless from here.
Pergi tanpa langkah dari sini.
You took my son away.
Anda membawa anak saya pergi.
Come on Osman.
Ayo Osman.
Go stepless from here.
Pergi tanpa langkah dari sini.
Come on!
Ayo!
Kademsiz!
Kademsiz!
Osman!
Osman!
It could be a trap.
Itu bisa menjadi jebakan.
Nobody knows we're going through here, Commander Balgay.
Tidak ada yang tahu kita akan lewat sini, Komandan Balgay.
Who knows where we're going ...
Siapa yang tahu kemana kita akan pergi ...
Kongar predicts the way we will pass.
Kongar memprediksi jalan yang akan kita lewati.
Unless the skies desire ...
Kecuali keinginan langit ...
... happy trees don't fall over.
... pohon bahagia tidak jatuh.
Enemy ...
Musuh ...
... unless the evil spirits touch the hand ...
... kecuali roh-roh jahat menyentuh tangan ...
... happy trees ...
... pohon bahagia ...
... standing upright.
... berdiri tegak.
Remove.
Hapus.
Balgay.
Balgay.
Osman.
Osman.
What is that...
Apa itu ...
... are you surprised?
... apakah kamu terkejut?
After that, to you ...
Setelah itu, untukmu ...
... lay hot on black soil ...
... Berbaring panas di tanah hitam ...
... to get up cold.
... bangun dingin.
Let the albums collapse Osman on the carcass.
Biarkan albumnya meruntuhkan Osman di bangkai.
You came to Oba with the wrath of Mongolian.
Anda datang ke Oba dengan amarah Mongolia.
Me too, the innocents you slaughtered ...
Aku juga, orang tak berdosa yang kau bunuh ...
I came with revenge.
Saya datang dengan pembalasan.
Anger's ...
Kemarahan adalah ...
... bigger than revenge.
... lebih besar dari balas dendam.
Come on, Osman!
Ayo, Osman!
We are not afraid of death.
Kami tidak takut mati.
He fights with our faith ...
Dia berkelahi dengan iman kita ...
... we chase martyrdom.
... kita mengejar mati syahid.
Allahu akbar!
Allahu akbar!
[Generic]
[Generik]